UNITE Muzaffar Chishti Papers 6000/047
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Muzaffar Chishti Papers
1991-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Chishti, Muzaffar
6000/047
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers.
6992255
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications 6000/046: UNITE Immigration Project Records 6000/054: UNITE Immigration Project Records
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Organizaiton; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Chishti, Muzaffar; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees.; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6992255
- ID/LM CF Contract Language, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ID/LM CF Audit, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ID/LM CAF Boston, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ID/LM CF Amalgamated Bank, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ID/LM CF Bank Statement, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ID/LM CF Board Meeting, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ID/LM CF Contributing Firms, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ID/LM CF Ergonomics, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ID/LM CF GIDC Funding, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ID/LM CF Income/Expense Summary, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ID/LM CF Philadelphia, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ID/LM CF Tax Return, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ID/LM CF Vouchers (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ID/LM Department of Commerce, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ID/LM Engineering/Managing Services, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ID/LM Fashion Center BID, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)